go-chan.blogspot.com 2018-12-24

# Go-chan โกจัง: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We will never sell your personal information to third parties without your solicitation.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

**Log Files**  
As with most other web servers on the internet, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include which website you were referred from, your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We also employ third party tracking services such as Google Analytics, which collects similar information to provide us with an offsite clean interface to look at our statistics. You can read how Google protects your privacy on their own privacy policy.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies to store information for your convenience to save color preferences. We also use third party advertisements on go-chan.blogspot.com. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can greatly affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as most other websites. This could include the inability to login to our website for longer than a single browser session.
